从字符串中除去重复项
Removing duplicate from a string
是从数组中移动重复项的功能等价项。
is the functional equivalent of
moving duplicate from an array.
因为我们在前一个例子中了解到，
Because we learned in
the previous example,
我们如何把任何东西转换成阵列
how we can convert
anything into the array.
所以我要开始我需要一个功能
So I'm gonna start with,
I need a function that takes a string so
调用 removeDuplicates (str) ，并在此处获取字符串，并获取字符串，并且
called removeDuplicates (str) and it take
string here and it takes a string, and
它将会返回一些新的字符串
it's going to return some new string.
一个解决这个问题的方法就是
One approach this problem
would be to take the string,
将其转换为数组，创建新的数组。
convert it into an array,
create a new array.
每次你进入一个你没有进入过的地方
And then every time you run into something
that you haven't run into before,
你只会推着这个新阵列
you just push that new array.
所以如果我们要从精神上走
So if we're gonna walk through
this mentally, I mean this,
我没看到这个因为我的阵列在这里是空的
I haven't seen this because my
array is empty at this point.
我要把这个推到新阵列上
I'm gonna push this to the new array and
I'm gonna say every
在那个循环上我只是在迭代这个阵列
single time on that loop,
I'm just iterating over this array,
我可以说新的 array. 包括或 indexOf?
I can say does the new array.includes or
indexOf?
我知道，我想我怎么能在阵列上迭代呢 ?
I know, it's thinking like how
can I iterate over the array?
如果你用双四圈来保持阵列的话
If you did it kind of with a double
four loop as in keeping the array,
那就好这是个解决办法
that's fine, it's a solution.
它不是最佳的但它是一种解决方案
It's not optimal but it's a solution and
当你想到 " array " 的时候，包括在技术上是做同样的事情。
when you think about array.includes is
technically sort of doing the same thing.
只是在幕后做，但速度要快得多
It's just doing it behind the scenes but
it's much faster so
这才是解决问题的方法
that's one solution and that would work.
同样的事情也会发生在我的工作上
The same thing would work for
number strings or anything, I'm gonna take
使用现代的 JavaScripts ，并使用不同的数据结构。
advantage of modern JavaScripts and
use a different data structure.
这就是我不会说的因为任何其他的解决方案都能起作用
And this was kind of I won't say a trick
because any other solution will work
迭代使用四环，这一方式更有效率。
iterating use the four loop,
this way is a little bit more efficient.
我要做的第一件事就是为我的弦线制作一个阵列
So first thing I'm gonna do is I'm
gonna create an array for my string, so
我要说的是 string.splits。
I'm gonna say, string.splits.
所以我要有一套新的字串我想说
So I'm going to get a new array
of every string, I'm gonna say,
做这只长手
doing this long hand.
我要用一套规则在 JavaScript中做什么
I'm gonna use a set rule,
what does a set do in JavaScript?
嗯。
Yes.
>> 它类似于数组，但不能重复。
&gt;&gt; It's like an array but
cannot have duplicate.
>> 是，设置的 JavaScript 中的数据结构不能重复
&gt;&gt; Yes, set is a data structure in
JavaScript that can not have duplicate
我可以说新的一套然后我就能通过我的阵列了
items so I can say new set And
then, I'm gonna pass in my array.
我觉得你可以把琴弦变成一套
I think you could actually
pass in a string into a set,
它可能决定实际工作我还没试过呢
it might decide actually work,
I haven't tried that yet.
但为了安全我们就有一套
But just to be safe,
we have a set and then,
我准备好了我要打个新电话
I'm gonna take the set, and
I'm gonna call create a new string.
所以我要说新字符串是
So I'm gonna say newString is,
我要把我的集合转换成数组
I need to convert my set
back into an array so
我可以用一个 array.from ，或者我要用一个传播算子，因为它是 " fanancer" 。
I can use an array.from or I'm gonna use
a spread operator because it's fancier.
那就得把所有重复数据都删除了
So that's gonna take that set which
now has all duplicates removed,
转换回数组。
converted back to array.
现在我需要将它转换为字符串，所以我要说 string.join。
Now I need to convert it back into
a string so I'm gonna say string.join.
谢谢你的 VS .
Thank you VS code for helping me there.
并且您有一个函数，该函数采用数组并除去所有重复项。
And there you have a function that takes
an array and removes all the duplicates.
所以如果你用这四环并使用额外的数组，也就可以了，
So if you use the four loop and
use the additional array, that's fine too,
那是个完美的解决方法
that is a perfectly good solution.
这个集合有点小 ancer ，我可能都是在一条线上
The set is a little bit fancier, I could
actually probably do this all in one line
如果我真的想这样做但我不是为了太复杂了
if I really wanted to, but I I'm not doing
it for the sake of being too complicated.
那就没那么糟了
So that wasn't too bad and
希望我们能把任何事都转化为雷
hopefully now we're building up to
I can convert anything into Ray and
然后转换成不同的数据结构做任何我想做的事情。
then do whatever I want once it's
converted to a different data structure.
这也是一个很好的问题，如果你知道你的数据结构，
This is also good question for
if you know your data structures,
它会帮你不用你不用背什么地图和地图
it will help you don't have to, you don't
have to memorize what maps and sets and
脆弱的地图和类似的东西
weak maps are and things like that.
但对这样的问题很有帮助
But it's helpful for questions like these.
但是一般的宝石小费如果有什么独特的价值
But a general gem tip, if there's
something saying unique values use a set,
它会为你做所有的工作
it does all the work for you.